[Music]
case briefs and so much more LS status
got what you're looking for
a complex class action lawsuit against
Prudential Insurance regarding deceptive
sales practices led to federal courts
stepping in to prevent relitigation of
claims in order to protect the Integrity
of the settlement
the Nationwide class consisting of over
8 million Prudential policyholders
excluded certain policies which prompted
the plaintiffs to file separate lawsuits
in Florida
The District Court then issued an
injunction prohibiting these
policyholders from pursuing related
lawsuits a decision which was later
affirmed by the court of appeals
this ruling established that the
district court had the jurisdiction to
oversee the settlement issue injunctions
and protect judgments with the goal of
preventing the undermining of
multi-district settlements and the risk
of defendants being exposed to multiple
State Court suits
[Music]
hide